<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to my second brain</title>
    <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome to my second brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:37:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teaching History</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/sywt-teach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/sywt-teach/</guid>
      <description>How should we be teaching history? Reasons The Usual Suspects  Broaden horizons Show how society changes  Reality We are passing on the torch of Human history.
Content Methods    American West WW1 Medicine Elizabeth     [[American West Lessons]] [[WW1 Lessons]] [[Medicine Lessons]] [[Elizabeth Lessons]]   [[Model GCSE answers American West]] [[Model GCSE Answers WW1]] [[Model GCSE Answers Medicine]] [[Model GCSE Answers Elizabeth]]          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching History</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachinghistory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachinghistory/</guid>
      <description>How should we be teaching history? Reasons The Usual Suspects  Broaden horizons Show how society changes  Reality We are passing on the torch of Human history.
Content Methods    American West WW1 Medicine Elizabeth     [[American West Lessons]] [[WW1 Lessons]] [[Medicine Lessons]] [[Elizabeth Lessons]]   [[Model GCSE answers American West]] [[Model GCSE Answers WW1]] [[Model GCSE Answers Medicine]] [[Model GCSE Answers Elizabeth]]          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Teaching</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachingguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachingguide/</guid>
      <description>Caveats  This information is provided as a collection of random pointers that have worked well for me over the years This list is meant not as a checklist but merely pointers that have helped in and around school Some, most or all of which you may not agree with   In the Classroom  Wait for silence Fill a spray bottle with water, keep your whiteboard clean Have pupils perform tasks, hand out books, clean your room Number seats and books, helps with hands down questioning and book distribution When taking books in, have students open them at exactly where you will be marking  Working with technology  Printing - learn how to scan and leave a post for people Have a collection of coloured paper next to the printer for SEND Create email templates for typical emails such as detentions, reprographics and parents Control Q on SIMS Control Shift V will paste without formatting Keep records, establish a habit of scanning work -  Working with colleagues  Do not gossip If parents  Outside school  There will come times when you meet pupils outside of school, and for the most part it will be a smile nod, a smile or some other for of acknowledgment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Beauty2</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/truebeauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/truebeauty/</guid>
      <description>Love Triangle Academics Beauty Peer Pressure  Is love worth dying for? We all have inner demons</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to move on</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/timetomoveon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/timetomoveon/</guid>
      <description>References  My Emotions Observations    If you are not moving forward you are regressing.
  9 years in one school 192*4 768 768 lessons per years 6912 lessons   I am still early in my career but an interview would have been nice. The initial hit of being told less than 72 hours after submitted the application that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t made the cut for interview was tough; I thought at the very least I had earnt that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madness of Crowds</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/madnessofcrowds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/madnessofcrowds/</guid>
      <description>Author Douglas Murray Reading Status: Read Date Finished July 1st, 2020 Why Fan of the author. How society interacts    Tags:: #Book #woke #gender #race #identity #gay #sexuality #interaction #InterpersonalRelationships #norms #truth #socialmedia #bias     Key Highlight:: - &amp;ldquo;‘[[Identity politics]]’, meanwhile, has become the place where social justice finds its caucuses. It atomizes society into different interest groups according to sex (or #gender), #race, sexual preference and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Your Work</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/showyourwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/showyourwork/</guid>
      <description>Key Take Aways      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading  This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Count of Monte Cristo</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/countofmonte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/countofmonte/</guid>
      <description>I am not saying  That you should seek revenge That you should use escape from prison   This was a long read, set aside a good summer or, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, a number of hours on Audible (52 to be precise at x1 speed). This was an education in place names - there really are some books that are just off-putting, and I think if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t sped through the first chapter at x2 speed I would have put the book down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me?</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Chris On this site you will find my blog pertaining to teaching, society and my experiences
You will also find my notes and musing on a range of books, mostly non fiction
Thoughts and musings on Kdramas will also be discussed in the hope of converting more people away from Western Cinema
If any of the content has been helpful, feel free to Monzo Me a coffee
I do the following, but not in order or equal amounts   Pace around school as the person in charge of History Speak Chinese with a Tianjin accent Drink Trung Nguyen with a Vietnamese phin Highlight pdfs or books on Kindle with the intent of making detailed notes On the odd occasion i&amp;rsquo;ll make a YouTube video   If any of the above resonates with you, get in touch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Itaewon Class</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/itaweonclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/itaweonclass/</guid>
      <description>How to get revenge&amp;hellip; wait and then wait some more Take a peak into the social status hiearchy Yangban. On another day you think you could be watching the revenge tail from Parasite</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
