<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome to my second brain</title>
    <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Welcome to my second brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teaching History</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/teaching-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/teaching-history/</guid>
      <description>How should we be teaching history? Reasons The Usual Suspects  Broaden horizons Show how society changes  Reality We are passing on the torch of Human history.
Content Methods    American West WW1 Medicine Elizabeth     [[American West Lessons]] [[WW1 Lessons]] [[Medicine Lessons]] [[Elizabeth Lessons]]   [[Model GCSE answers American West]] [[Model GCSE Answers WW1]] [[Model GCSE Answers Medicine]] [[Model GCSE Answers Elizabeth]]          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White Liberal</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/malcolmx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/malcolmx/</guid>
      <description>The white liberal is the worst enemy to America, and the worst enemy to the black man. Let me explain what I mean by the white liberal. In America there is no such thing as Democrat or Republican anymore. In America you have liberals and conservatives. The only people living in the past who think in terms of I’m a Democrat or Republican, is the American Negro. He’s the one that runs around bragging about party affiliation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>True Beauty</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/korean/truebeauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/korean/truebeauty/</guid>
      <description>Love Triangle Academics Beauty Peer Pressure  Is love worth dying for? We all have inner demons</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to move on</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/timetomoveon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/timetomoveon/</guid>
      <description>References  My Emotions Observations    If you are not moving forward you are regressing.
  9 years in one school 192*4 768 768 lessons per years 6912 lessons   I am still early in my career but an interview would have been nice. The initial hit of being told less than 72 hours after submitted the application that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t made the cut for interview was tough; I thought at the very least I had earnt that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final 1%</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/final-1pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 23:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/final-1pc/</guid>
      <description>I am not saying  I am sad That&amp;hellip; I like dogs   My name is God
 https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW
!(https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW)
[https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW]
![interest] (https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW)
(images/madofc.jpg)
{% portfolio image=&amp;ldquo;images/madofc.jpg&amp;rdquo; alt=&amp;ldquo;Coder Portfolio&amp;rdquo; %}
82 years is the average lifespan of a male born in 1986. This would be 29,930 days or 299 (300) days.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say then you are in the final 1% or final 300days worth of time with those that brought you up - should that be if they havent left you already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn over your wrists</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/turn-over-your-wirst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/turn-over-your-wirst/</guid>
      <description>Quote 1) Seneca  Can you no longer see a road to freedom? It&amp;rsquo;s right in front of you. You need only turn over your wrists.
 Quote 2) 4chan  &amp;ldquo;I never got my people would kill themselves So if you want to die you obviously don&amp;rsquo;t give a shit. Like, about anyone. Because if there is anyone who loves you, you don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck about them, or hurting them, and if there is not, there is no one to give a shit about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madness of Crowds</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/madnessofcrowds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/madnessofcrowds/</guid>
      <description>Author Douglas Murray Reading Status: Read Date Finished July 1st, 2020 Why Fan of the author. How society interacts    Tags:: #Book #woke #gender #race #identity #gay #sexuality #interaction #InterpersonalRelationships #norms #truth #socialmedia #bias     Key Highlight:: - &amp;ldquo;‘[[Identity politics]]’, meanwhile, has become the place where social justice finds its caucuses. It atomizes society into different interest groups according to sex (or #gender), #race, sexual preference and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Your Work</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/showyourwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/showyourwork/</guid>
      <description>Key Take Aways      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech and Teaching</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Remember that CPD day, the one where the member of SLT had chosen to link a YouTube video in the PPT? Remember when the URL was clicked. Remember how, because it was in presentation mode the browser of the day (it was IE, let’s be real) played the video behind the Presentation? I do.
I do because said member of staff was then at a loss for several minutes, for me it was an epoch, as to why there was sound but no video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Count of Monte Cristo</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/countofmonte/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/books/countofmonte/</guid>
      <description>I am not saying  That you should seek revenge That you should use escape from prison   This was a long read, set aside a good summer or, let&amp;rsquo;s be honest, a number of hours on Audible (52 to be precise at x1 speed). This was an education in place names - there really are some books that are just off-putting, and I think if I hadn&amp;rsquo;t sped through the first chapter at x2 speed I would have put the book down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Me?</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Chris On this site you will find my blog pertaining to teaching, society and my experiences
You will also find my notes and musing on a range of books, mostly non fiction
Thoughts and musings on Kdramas will also be discussed in the hope of converting more people away from Western Cinema
I do the following, but not in order or equal amounts   Pace around school as the person in charge of History Speak Chinese with a Tianjin accent Drink Trung Nguyen with a Vietnamese phin Highlight pdfs or books on Kindle with the intent of making detailed notes On the odd occasion i&amp;rsquo;ll make a YouTube video   If any of the above resonates with you, get in touch</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Itaewon Class</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/korean/itaweonclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/korean/itaweonclass/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
