<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teachings on Welcome to my second brain</title>
    <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teachings on Welcome to my second brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:37:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Teaching History</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/sywt-teach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 19:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/sywt-teach/</guid>
      <description>How should we be teaching history? Reasons The Usual Suspects  Broaden horizons Show how society changes  Reality We are passing on the torch of Human history.
Content Methods    American West WW1 Medicine Elizabeth     [[American West Lessons]] [[WW1 Lessons]] [[Medicine Lessons]] [[Elizabeth Lessons]]   [[Model GCSE answers American West]] [[Model GCSE Answers WW1]] [[Model GCSE Answers Medicine]] [[Model GCSE Answers Elizabeth]]          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching History</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachinghistory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 13:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachinghistory/</guid>
      <description>How should we be teaching history? Reasons The Usual Suspects  Broaden horizons Show how society changes  Reality We are passing on the torch of Human history.
Content Methods    American West WW1 Medicine Elizabeth     [[American West Lessons]] [[WW1 Lessons]] [[Medicine Lessons]] [[Elizabeth Lessons]]   [[Model GCSE answers American West]] [[Model GCSE Answers WW1]] [[Model GCSE Answers Medicine]] [[Model GCSE Answers Elizabeth]]          </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Teaching</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachingguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/teachingguide/</guid>
      <description>Caveats  This information is provided as a collection of random pointers that have worked well for me over the years This list is meant not as a checklist but merely pointers that have helped in and around school Some, most or all of which you may not agree with   In the Classroom  Wait for silence Fill a spray bottle with water, keep your whiteboard clean Have pupils perform tasks, hand out books, clean your room Number seats and books, helps with hands down questioning and book distribution When taking books in, have students open them at exactly where you will be marking  Working with technology  Printing - learn how to scan and leave a post for people Have a collection of coloured paper next to the printer for SEND Create email templates for typical emails such as detentions, reprographics and parents Control Q on SIMS Control Shift V will paste without formatting Keep records, establish a habit of scanning work -  Working with colleagues  Do not gossip If parents  Outside school  There will come times when you meet pupils outside of school, and for the most part it will be a smile nod, a smile or some other for of acknowledgment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to move on</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/timetomoveon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 22:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/teaching/timetomoveon/</guid>
      <description>References  My Emotions Observations    If you are not moving forward you are regressing.
  9 years in one school 192*4 768 768 lessons per years 6912 lessons   I am still early in my career but an interview would have been nice. The initial hit of being told less than 72 hours after submitted the application that I hadn&amp;rsquo;t made the cut for interview was tough; I thought at the very least I had earnt that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
