<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Welcome to my second brain</title>
    <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome to my second brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The White Liberal</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/malcolmx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 20:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/malcolmx/</guid>
      <description>The white liberal is the worst enemy to America, and the worst enemy to the black man. Let me explain what I mean by the white liberal. In America there is no such thing as Democrat or Republican anymore. In America you have liberals and conservatives. The only people living in the past who think in terms of I’m a Democrat or Republican, is the American Negro. He’s the one that runs around bragging about party affiliation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time to move on</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/timetomoveon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/timetomoveon/</guid>
      <description>References  TTC The Great War (Liulevicius) BBC Bitesize    If you are not moving forward you are regressing.
 9 years in one school 192*4 768 768 lessons per years
6912 lessons
 So first i was rejected for an SLT position, i am still early in my career but an interview would have been nice.
 &amp;ldquo;France sought allies with which to oppose Germany.&amp;rdquo; (Liulevicius :161)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn over your wrists</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/turn-over-your-wirst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/turn-over-your-wirst/</guid>
      <description>Quote 1) Seneca  Can you no longer see a road to freedom? It&amp;rsquo;s right in front of you. You need only turn over your wrists.
 Quote 2) 4chan  &amp;ldquo;I never got my people would kill themselves So if you want to die you obviously don&amp;rsquo;t give a shit. Like, about anyone. Because if there is anyone who loves you, you don&amp;rsquo;t give a fuck about them, or hurting them, and if there is not, there is no one to give a shit about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final 1%</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/final-1pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/final-1pc/</guid>
      <description>title: &amp;ldquo;Final 1%&amp;rdquo; date: 2021-02-07T23:40:41Z categories: [&amp;lsquo;Reflection&amp;rsquo;] draft: true I am not saying  I am sad That&amp;hellip; I like dogs   My name is God
 https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW
!(https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW)
[https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW]
![interest] (https://imgur.com/5M6qtYW)
(images/madofc.jpg)
{% portfolio image=&amp;ldquo;images/madofc.jpg&amp;rdquo; alt=&amp;ldquo;Coder Portfolio&amp;rdquo; %}
82 years is the average lifespan of a male born in 1986. This would be 29,930 days or 299 (300) days.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say then you are in the final 1% or final 300days worth of time with those that brought you up - should that be if they havent left you already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech and Teaching</title>
      <link>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://khongsao.github.io/cblog.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Remember that CPD day, the one where the member of SLT had chosen to link a YouTube video in the PPT? Remember when the URL was clicked. Remember how, because it was in presentation mode the browser of the day (it was IE, let’s be real) played the video behind the Presentation? I do.
I do because said member of staff was then at a loss for several minutes, for me it was an epoch, as to why there was sound but no video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
